Flight 93 is a drama, thriller, tv movie film directed by Peter Markle.
Flight 93 is a 2006 made-for-TV film, directed by Peter Markle, which chronicles the
events aboard United Airlines Flight 93 during the September 11 attacks.
It premiered January 30, 2006 on the A&E Network and was
re-broadcast several times throughout 2006.
The film focused heavily on eight passengers, namely Todd Beamer, Mark Bingham, Tom Burnett, Jeremy
Glick, Lauren Grandcolas, Donald Greene, Nicole Miller, and Honor Elizabeth Wainio.
It features small appearances from many other passengers, namely Donald Peterson
and his wife, Jean, and also from flight attendant Sandra Bradshaw.
Tom Burnett, played by Jeffrey Nordling.
Todd Beamer, played by Brennan Elliott.
Deena Burnett, played by Kendall Cross.
Mark Bingham, played by Ty Olsson.
Lisa Jefferson, played by Monnae Michaell.
Ahmed Alnami, played by Asim Wali.
Flight 93 is a 2006 American drama television film directed by Peter Markle and written by Nevin Schreiner, which
chronicles the events onboard United Airlines Flight 93 during the September 11 attacks in 2001.
It premiered on January 30, 2006, on A&E, and was
re-broadcast several times throughout 2006.
The film stars Jeffrey Nordling, Colin Glazer, Brennan Elliott, Ty Olsson,
Jacqueline Ann Steuart, Laura Mennell, Karen Holness, Barry W.
Levy, Biski Gugushe, and Dominic Rains.
The film explores themes of airplane, war on terror, passenger, terrorism, 9/11.
The tone is emotional and intense.